A Guide to the University of Virginia Hospital Executive Director's Office (HEDO) Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- AGREEMENT FOR ROTATION OF EMERGENCY MEDICAL SUPPLIES & CORRESPONDENCE 1967 - 1968, TLS, carbon copy TL, TMs (Box-folder 6:011)
- EMERGENCY PREPAREDNESS & PROCEDURE: CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1968, TLS (2), TL (1) (Box-folder 6:012)
- HEALTH SECTION: CHARLOTTESVILLE EMERGENCY RESOURCE MANAGEMENT PLAN 1969, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 6:013)
- CITY OF CHARLOTTESVILLE EMERGENCY RESOURCE MANAGEMENT PLAN, FINAL DRAFT January 1969, TMs (Box-folder 6:014)
- USE OF HOSPITAL DISASTER PROGRAM DURING FOOD POISONING INCIDENT OF 9-25-59 September 25, 1959, TMs (Box-folder 6:015)
- USE OF THE HOSPITAL DISASTER PROGRAM DURING THE TORNADO INCIDENT OF 9-30-59 September 30, 1959, TMs (Box-folder 6:016)
- HOSPITAL DISASTER PLAN IN CONNECTION WITH PIEDMONT AIRPLANE CRASH October 30, 1959, TMs (Box-folder 6:017)
- USE OF HOSPITAL DISASTER PLAN DURING BUS ACCIDENT OF 5-1-62 May 1, 1962, TMs (Box-folder 6:018)
- UVA HOSPITAL'S RESPONSE TO BUS WRECK April 28, 1964, TLS (Box-folder 6:019)
- SIMULATED DISASTER DRILL OF 9-22-65 AT SCOTT STADIUM 1965, TL (Box-folder 6:020)
- PHOTOGRAPHS OF THE EMERGENCY DRILL AT SCOTT STADIUM September 22, 1965, Photo (10) (Box-folder 6:021)
- SIMULATED DISASTER AT SCOTT STADIUM September 1965, Newsclipping (4) (Box-folder 6:022)
- PARTIAL IMPLEMENTATION OF DISASTER PLAN AT UVA HOSPITAL July 1966, TMs (Box-folder 6:023)
  RE: AUTO ACCIDENT 7-3-66
- UVA HOSPITAL'S RESPONSE TO UNSUBSTANTIATED BOMB THREAT January 1968, TL (1), TMs (Box-folder 6:024)
- SCHOOL BUS ACCIDENT May 17, 1968, TLS (Box-folder 6:025)
- LISTS OF BODIES FROM FLOOD IN NELSON COUNTY September 1969, ALS (1), TLS (1), TMs (Box-folder 6:026)
- SCHOOL BUS-CAR ACCIDENT ON JANUARY 29, 1970 January 29, 1970, TLS, Newsclipping (Box-folder 6:027)
- DISASTER DRILL AT UVA HOSPITAL March 1970, TMs (Box-folder 6:028)
- SIMULATED DISASTER DRILL-MOCK AIRPLANE CRASH March 14, 1970, Newsclipping (Box-folder 6:029)
- PARTIAL IMPLEMENTATION OF DISASTER PLAN: CAR ACCIDENT August 1, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 6:030)
- SIMULATED CHLORINE DISASTER IN CHARLOTTESVILLE, 10-12-75 October 1975, TMs (Box-folder 6:031)
- MEMORANDUM & CALL LIST: CIVIL DEFENSE EXERCISE October 1975, TMs (Box-folder 6:032)
- SCENARIO: SPECIAL EXERCISE OF HOSPITALS AND RESCUE SQUAD November 2, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 6:033)
  RE: SIMULATED CHLORINE DISASTER
- HEALTH SERVICES CRITIQUE OF CHLORINE DISASTER EXERCISE HELD ON 11-2-75 November - December 1975, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 6:034)
- INVESTIGATION OF CHLORINE EXPOSURES IN LOUISIANA, TMs (Box-folder 6:035)
- REPORT ON THE RELEASE OF CHLORINE AT LABARRE, LA. ON 1-31-61 1961?, TMs (Box-folder 6:036)
- CHLORINE DISASTERS 1963 - 1965, Newsclippings (Box-folder 6:037)
- MEDICAL ARTICLES ON CHLORINE 1963 - 1970, Newsclippings (Box-folder 6:038)
- MATERIAL SAFETY DATA SHEET: CHLORINE November 1974, TDoc, Questionairre (Box-folder 6:039)
- TRAIN DISASTER IN NELSON COUNTY CORRESPONDENCE December 1978, TL, TLS (Box-folder 6:040)
- UVA INFORMATION SERVICE AND UNIVERSITY RELATIONS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1970, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 6:041)
- MINUTES & NOTES OF THE UNIVERSITY RELATIONS COMMITTEE 1970, TMs (Box-folder 6:042)
  RE: VARIA PUBLIC RELATIONS PROBLEMS & ADMISSIONS OF WOMEN & AFRICAN -AMERICANS TO THE MEDICAL SCHOOL
- COMMUNITY HEALTH RESEARCH TRAINING PROGRAM FINAL REPORT 1966, TMs (Box-folder 6:043)
  STATUS OF NURSING HOME CARE & HOME HEALTH SERVICES IN CHARLOTTESVILLE
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH STATE DEPT. OF HEALTH 1944 - 1947, TLS (2), TL, TMs (Box-folder 7:001)
  HOSPITAL SANITATION INSPECTIONS & PUBLIC HEALTH INFORMATION
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH STATE DEPT. OF HEALTH 1948 - 1950, TLS (2), TL, TMs (Box-folder 7:002)
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH STATE DEPT. OF HEALTH 1965 - 1978, TLS (2), ALS (1), TL, TMs (Box-folder 7:003)
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH CHARLOTTESVILLE-ALBERMARLE HEALTH DEPT. 1948 - 1950, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 7:004)
  RE:JOINT HEALTH DEPTARTMENT-HOSPITAL INSPECTIONS
- ALBERMARLE-CHARLOTTESVILLE HEALTH DEPARTMENT ANNUAL REPORT March 30, 1970, Newsclipping (Box-folder 7:005)
- PROCEEDINGS OF THE CONFERENCE ON CRIPPLED CHILDREN AT MEDICAL COLLEGE OF VIRGINIA, RICHMOND September 27-28, 1951, Booklet (Box-folder 7:006)
- BUREAU OF CRIPPLED CHILDREN, STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH: CORRESPONDENCE WITH UVA HOSPITAL 1953 - 1960, TLS (2), ALS, TL (Box-folder 7:007)
- BUREAU OF CRIPPLED CHILDREN, STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH: CORRESPONDENCE WITH UVA HOSPITAL 1962 - 1965, TLS (2), TL (1), ALS (1) (Box-folder 7:008)
- BUREAU OF CRIPPLED CHILDREN, STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH: CORRESPONDENCE WITH UVA HOSPITAL 1966 - 1975, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 7:009)
- BUREAU OF CRIPPLED CHILDREN, STATE DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH: CORRESPONDENCE WITH UVA HOSPITAL 1978, TLS (2), ALS, TMs (Box-folder 7:010)
- CORRESPONDENCE WITH DEPT. OF HEALTH, DIVISION OF ALCOHOL STUDIES & REHABILITATION 1954 - 1965, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 7:011)
- VIRGINIA DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH HOSPITAL & NURSING HOME CORRESPONDENCE 1949 - 1950, TL, TLS (Box-folder 7:012)
  LICENSING SECTION
- NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF HEALTH CORRESPONDENCE 1964 - 1965, TLS (2), TM (Box-folder 7:013)
- NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF HEALTH CORRESPONDENCE February 1965, TM (2), TLS (Box-folder 7:014)
  OPERATING REPORT FOR UVA HOSPITAL, 1964
- NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF HEALTH March - October 1965, TM, TL (Box-folder 7:015)
- BLOOD BANK 1949 - 1959, ALS, TLS, TL, TM (Box-folder 7:016)
- BLOOD BANK CORRESPONDENCE 1960 - 1978, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 7:017)
- BLOOD BANK COMMITTEE: RECORDS OF BLOOD REPLACEMENT BY SERVICES 1949 - 1958, TMs (Box-folder 7:018)
- BLOOD BANK ANNUAL REPORT TO THE CLINICAL STAFF July 1957 - June 1959, TMs (Box-folder 7:019)
- BLOOD BANK ANNUAL REPORT TO THE CLINICAL STAFF July 1959 - June 1962, TMs (Box-folder 7:020)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA BLOOD BANK ANNUAL REPORT July 1962 - June 1966, TMs (Box-folder 7:021)
- BLOOD BANK COMMITTEE: RECORD OF BLOOD REPLACEMENT SERVICES 1975, TMs (Box-folder 7:022)
- STARTING AND OPERATING A BLOOD BANK 1951, Pamphlet (Box-folder 7:023)
- RED CROSS BLOOD PROGRAM: QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS 1952, Pamphlet (Box-folder 7:024)
- A NEW NATION-WIDE PIPELINE-FOR BLOOD & UNIVERSITY REGISTER 1957, 1983, Pamphlets (Box-folder 7:025)
- BLOOD BANK 1964, 1969, Newsclippings (Box-folder 7:026)
- PREVENTORIUM: LEGAL CONTRACT TO ORGANIZE & FUND A NEW PREVENTORIUM March 1931, TL, TMs (Box-folder 7:027)
- PREVENTORIUM: CORRESPONDENCE 1962 - 1966, TMs, TL, TLS (2), AMS (Box-folder 7:028)
- PREVENTORIUM CORRESPONDENCE 1967 - 1968, TL, ALS, TMs, TLS (2), Newsclipping (Box-folder 7:029)
- PREVENTORIUM CORRESPONDENCE 1969 - 1970, ALS (2), TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 7:030)
- PREVENTORIUM: STATEMENT OF RECEIPTS, DISBURSEMENTS & BALANCE FOR THE 6 MONTHS PERRIOD ENDED 12-31-67 1965 - 1967, TMs (Box-folder 7:031)
- PREVENTORIUM: STATEMENT OF RECEIPTS, DISBURSEMENTS & BALANCE FOR THE 10 MONTHS PERIOD ENDED 4-30-70 1968 - 1970, TMs (Box-folder 7:032)
- PREVENTORIUM OPERATING FUND: PROPOSED BUDGETS 1965 - 1967, TMs (Box-folder 7:033)
- PREVENTORIUM: ESTIMATES OF PROFESSIONAL FEES FOR DIAGNOSTIC WORK-UPS AND/OR PHYSICAL EXAMINATIONS July 1967, ALS, TM (Box-folder 7:034)
- A 6 MONTH SURVEY BY DEPARTMENTS OF POSSIBLE FINANCIAL LOSSES IN TREATMENT OF PREVENTORIUM PATIENTS 1965 - 1966, TMs, AMs (Box-folder 7:035)
- UVA HOSPITAL MEDICAL POLICY COMMITTEE MINUTES April 19, 1966, TMs (Box-folder 7:036)
  RE: PREVENTORIUM
- SURVEYS OF PREVENTORIUM IN-PATIENTS 1962 - 1963, 1966, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 7:037)
- SURVEY OF PATIENTS & CHARGES, CLINIC, PRIVATE DIVISION, PREVENTORIUM June 1967, TMs (Box-folder 7:038)
- RESOLUTION February 1966, TMs (Box-folder 7:039)
  POLICY CHANGES FOR PREVENTION
- PREVENTORIUM COMMITTEE MEETING May 15, 1964, TMs (Box-folder 7:040)
- PREVENTORIUM COMMITTEE MEETING May 10, 1965, TMs (Box-folder 7:041)
- PREVENTORIUM COMMITTEE MEETING May 14, 1966, Pamphlets (2), TMs (Box-folder 7:042)
  INCLUDES CONTENTS OF A CONFERENCE PACKET
- REPORT OF SPECIAL COMMITTEE TO STUDY PREVENTORIUM OPERATIONS March 1967 - July 1967, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 7:043)
- PREVENTORIUM COMMITTEE MEETING May 12, 1967, TMs (Box-folder 7:044)
- PREVENTORIUM COMMITTEE MINUTES May 24, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 7:045)
- PREVENTORIUM COMMITTEE MEETING 5-12-69 May 1969, Article Offprint (Box-folder 7:046)
- VEA PREVENTORIUM FOR TEACHERS June 1965, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:001)
- PREVENTORIUM-MISCELLANEOUS ITEMS 1964 - 1969, Newsclipping, TMs (Box-folder 8:002)
- GENERAL ADMINISTRATION POLICIES AND PROCEDURES July 1973, Pamphlet (xerox copy) (Box-folder 8:003)
  RE: HOSPITAL ACCREDITATION
- INTERIM SELF SURVEY PROGRESS REPORT; RECOMMENDATIONS FROM THE JOINT COMMISSION ON ACCREDITATION OF HOSPITALS 1974, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 8:004)
- ACCREDITATION ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES January 27, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:005)
- ACCREDITATION ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES February 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:006)
  ACCREDITATION MANUAL FOR HOSPITALS
- ACCREDITATION ADVISORY COMMITTEE MEETING MINUTES June 23, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:007)
- ACCREDITATION ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES July 28, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:008)
- ACCREDITATION ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES September 21, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:009)
- ACCREDITATION ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES November 24, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:010)
- ADMINISTRATIVE POLICY COMMITTEE MINUTES March - June 1951, TMs (Box-folder 8:011)
- ADMINISTRATIVE POLICY COMMITTEE MINUTES July - December 1951, TL, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 8:012)
- ADMINISTRATIVE POLICY COMMITTEE MINUTES January - June 1952, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:013)
- ADMINISTRATIVE POLICY COMMITTEE MINUTES September - December 1952, TMs (Box-folder 8:014)
- ADMINISTRATIVE POLICY COMMITTEE MINUTES January - May 1953, TMs (Box-folder 8:015)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL SURVEY NEW PATIENT CARE FACILITIES December 1966, TL, TMs, Patient Records (Box-folder 8:016)
- FACILITIES PLANNING COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1966 - 1967, TL (2), TLS (Box-folder 8:017)
- CORRESPONDENCE: BED ALLOCATION 1971 - 1974, TL, TLS (2), TMs, AMs (Box-folder 8:018)
- COMMITTEE ON THE RE-ALIGNMENT OF HOSPITAL BEDS MINUTES Decemebr 18, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:019)
- STATISTICAL REPORT ON BED OCCUPANCY 1967 - 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:020)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL YEARLY STATISTICAL REPORT June 1969 - June 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:021)
- BED UTILIZATION COMMITTEE MINUTES February 23, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:022)
- BED UTILIZATION COMMITTEE REPORT May 18, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:023)
- REPORT OF THE AD HOC COMMITTEE TO REVIEW HOSPITAL BED ASSIGNMENT & BED UTILISATION AND ADMITTING POLICIES September 1973, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 8:024)
- STATISTICS ADMISSIONS & BED UTILISATION 1971 - 1973, TMs (Box-folder 8:025)
- AD HOC COMMITTEE TO REVIEW HOSPITAL BED ASSIGNMENT & BED UTILISATION MINUTES February - March 1974, TMs (Box-folder 8:026)
- AD HOC COMMITTEE TO REVIEW HOSPITAL BED ASSIGNMENT & BED UTILISATION MINUTES April 1974 - June 1974, TMs (Box-folder 8:027)
- BED ASSIGNMENT COMMITTEE MINUTES November 17, 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:028)
- A MINIMAL CARE FACILITY FOR THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL: REPORT NO. 1 OF THE FACILITIES PLANNING COMMITTEE March 3, 1969, TMs (Box-folder 8:029)
- AN EXTENDED CARE FACILITY FOR THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL: REPORT NO. 2 OF THE FACILITIES PLANNING COMMITTEE May 31, 1967, TMs (Box-folder 8:030)
- FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES December 1970, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:031)
  SALARY OF HOUSE STAFF, HOUSE STAFF STATISTICS
- PROBLEMS INVOLVED IN THE BED ALLOCATION PROCESS 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:032)
- FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES July 14, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:033)
- FACULTY-HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MINUTES June 9, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:034)
- FORMULARY COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1942 - 1950, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 8:035)
- FACULTY HOUSE-STAFF COMMITTEE: PROPOSALS FOR CHANGES IN ADMISSIONS POLIC November 1970, TMs (Box-folder 8:036)
- UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL DIVISION FORMULARY, 1949 1949, Pamphlet (Box-folder 8:037)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING, FIFTH MEETING MINUTES November 14, 1967, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:038)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING REPORT ON MEETING December 8, 1967, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:039)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING, SIXTH MEETING MINUTES February 29, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 8:040)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING CORRESPONDENCE 1967 - 1969, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 8:041)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING SEVENTH MEETING MINUTES May 29, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 8:042)
- REPORT OF THE FIRST MEETING OF JOINT PLANNING COMMITTEE FOR CONFERENCE ON FUTURE PATTERNS OF HEALTH CARE November 13, 1967, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:043)
- TENTATIVE DRAFT OF PROPOSED STUDY OUTLINE FOR GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING July 1967, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:044)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING: SECOND DRAFT OF REPORT OF PROGRESS October 20, 1967, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 8:045)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING: POSSIBLE ITEMS FOR FINAL RECOMMENDATIONS April 4, 1968, TMs, Pamphlets (Box-folder 8:046)
- MINUTES OF THE ASEBLY MEETING, VIRGINIA HOSPITAL ASSOCITATION April 18, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 8:047)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING: TENTATIVE ITEMS FOR FINAL RECOMMENDATIONS OF COMMITTEE June 10-11, 1968, TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:048)
- STATEMENT OF THE AMERICAN HOSPITAL ASSOCIATION ON H.R. 15757, HEALTH MANPOWER ACT OF 1968 June 13, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 8:049)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING June 1968, ALS, TL, Article Offprint (Box-folder 8:050)
- BACKGROUND MATERIAL TO HELP COMMITTEE MEMBERS BETTER UNDERSTAND THE PHILOSOPHY AND OBJECTIVES AND FUNCTIONS OF THE BOARD OF NURSE EXAMINERS June 21, 1968, TMs (Box-folder 8:051)
  INFORMATION PACKET FOR GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING: QUESTIONAIRRE SURVEY ON NURSING PERSONNEL IN VIRGINIA HOSPITALS June & July 1968, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 8:052)
- GOVERNOR'S COMMITTEE ON NURSING: A REPORT OF PROGRESS December 1967, Pamphlet (Box-folder 8:053)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1959, TLS (2), TL, TMs (Box-folder 8:054)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1960 - 1962, TLS (2), TL (Box-folder 8:055)
- INFECTIONS COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE 1963 - 1974, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 8:056)
- HOSPITAL INFECTIONSCOMMITTEE MINUTES 1962 - 1975, TMs (Box-folder 8:057)
- SUMMARY REPORTS OF CHARTERED INFECTIONS BY MONTH 1962 - 1963, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 8:058)
- SUMMARY REPORTS OF CHARTED INFECTIONS BY MONTH January - July 1964, TL (2), TLS (1), TMs (Box-folder 8:059)
- PROCEDURES FOR ISOLATION OF PATIENTS AT UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA HOSPITAL 1964, TMs (Box-folder 8:060)
- A PROPOSAL FOR DATA PROCESSING SERVICES 1978, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 8:061)
  RE: INFECTION CONTROL
- PREVENTION AND CONTROL OF STAPHYLOCOCCUS INFECTIONS IN HOSPITALS May 21, 1958, Leaflets (Box-folder 8:062)
- INFECTIONS IN HOSPITALS August 1958, Leaflet (Box-folder 8:063)
- STAPHYLOCOCCUS INFECTION: AN ADDRESS 1959, Pamphlet (Box-folder 8:064)
- SURVEILLANCE OF HOSPITAL-ASSOCIATED INFECTIONS 1963, Newsclipping (Box-folder 8:065)
- WHAT IS THE LEGAL DUTY IN INFECTION CONTROL? July 1965, Newsclipping (Box-folder 8:066)
- THE ROLE OF THE HOSPITAL LABORATORY IN THE CONTROL OF INFECTION December 1966, Pamphlet reprint (Box-folder 8:067)
- CLINICAL ADVANCES: INFECTIOUS DISEASES 1969 - 1970, TL, Pamphlet (Box-folder 8:068)
- MINUTES OF THE INSURANCE AND HOUSE STAFF COMMITTEE MEETING December 18, 1961, TMs (Box-folder 8:069)
- MEDICAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES February 1973 - May 1973, TMs (Box-folder 9:001)
- MEDICAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES June 1973-September 1973, TMs (Box-folder 9:002)
- MEDICAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE MINUTES March 1974 - 1975, TMs (Box-folder 9:003)
- REPORT OF THE FIRST YEAR AND A HALF COMMITTEE TO THE MEDICAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE 1973, TMs (Box-folder 9:004)
- REPORT TO THE COUNCIL ON MEDICAL EDUCATION 1973, TMs (Box-folder 9:005)
  RE: EXPERIMENTAL CURRICULUM
- FIRST YEAR SCHEDULE, OCTOBER 8-DECEMBER 13, 1973-1974 1973, TMs (Box-folder 9:006)
- POLICIES AND GUIDELINES FOR UVA SCHOOL OF MEDICINE FACULTY APPOINTMENTS AND PROMOTIONS IN ROANOKE July 1973, TL, TMs (Box-folder 9:007)
- MEDICAL FEE SCHEDULE, APPROVED BY THE MEDICAL ADVISORY COMMITTEE OF THE VOCATIONAL REHABILITATION SERVICE 1953, TMs (Box-folder 9:008)
- RESUSCITATION COMMITTEE CORRESPONDENCE AND MINUTES 1971 - 1974, TL, TMs (Box-folder 9:009)
- PLAN FOR CARDIOPULMONARY RESUSCITATION 1965, TMs (Box-folder 9:010)
- ALLIED HEALTH PROFESSIONS CORRESPONDENCE FILE 1966 - 1972, TL (2), TLS (2), TMs, Pamphlet (Box-folder 9:011)
- COMMITTEE ON ALLIED HEALTH MINUTES November 1970, TMs (Box-folder 9:012)
- REPORT OF THE COMMITTEE ON ALLIED HEALTH PROFESSIONS July 1968, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 9:013)
- CONCLUSIONS OF THE COMMITTEE ON ALLIED HEALTH PROFESSIONS 1970, TMs (Box-folder 9:014)
- QUESTIONNAIRES FROM DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH AND WELFARE October 1965, TL (Box-folder 9:015)
- APPLICATIONS FOR TRAINING GRANTS FROM DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH, EDUCATION AND WELFARE 1967, TL, TLS (Box-folder 9:016)
- ANNOUNCEMENT OF APPLICATION PROCEDURES FOR THE ALLIED HEALTH PROFESSIONS BASIC IMPROVEMENT GRANT PROGRAM 1969, AN, TL, Article Offprint (Box-folder 9:017)
- AN ACT TO AMEND THE PUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE ACT November 3, 1966, TDoc (Box-folder 9:018)
- BULLETIN: DEPT. OF EDUCATION SERVICES, VA. HOSPITAL RESEARCH AND EDUCATION FOUNDATION 1969, Leaflet (Box-folder 9:019)
- UVA MEDICAL SCHOOL & SCHOOL OF RADIOLOGICAL TECHNOLOGY, Leaflets (Box-folder 9:020)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1958, TLS (2) (Box-folder 9:021)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, BIOGRAPHICAL DIRECTORY DEPARTMENT July 1953, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:022)
  RE: INTERNS AND RESIDENT PHYSICIANS
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, BIOGRAPHICAL DIRECTORY DEPARTMENT July 1954, TQuestionnaire (Box-folder 9:023)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, BIOGRAPHICAL DIRECTORY DEPARTMENT QUESTIONNAIRE August 1955, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:024)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, BIOGRAPHICAL DIRECTORY DEPARTMENT QUESTIONNAIRE 1956, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:025)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, BIOGRAPHICAL DIRECTORY DEPARTMENT QUESTIONNAIRE 1957, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:026)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, BIOGRAPHICAL DIRECTORY DEPARTMENT QUESTIONNAIRE August 1958, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:027)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, COUNCIL ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND HOSPITAL: HOSPITAL WORKSHEET-FELLOWSHIPS AND RESIDENCIES IN ANESTHESIOLOGY 1955, TMs (Box-folder 9:028)
- AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION, COUNCIL ON MEDICAL EDUCATION AND HOSPITALS, FELLOWSHIPS AND RESIDENCIES IN OTOLARYNGOLOGY 1959, TMs, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:029)
- COUNCIL ON MEDICAL EDUCATION & HOSPITALS: ANNUAL REPORT OF APPROVED SCHOOLS IN MEDICAL TECHNOLOGY 1953 - 1954, 1959, TMs, Questionnaire, TL (Box-folder 9:030)
  SURVEY OF APPROVED SCHOOLS IN MEDICAL TECHNOLOGY
- RESIDENCY POSITION REPORTS FROM UVA HOSPITAL 1953 - 1954, 1957, TL, Questionnaires (Box-folder 9:031)
  AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION QUESTIONNAIRE
- LIST OF SOME OPERATIONS PERFORMED BY MEMBERS OF THE DEPT. OF OTOLARYNGOLOGY 1952, AMs (Box-folder 9:0032)
  FROM AMERICAN MEDICAL ASSOCIATION FILE
- PUBLICATIONS IN THE PERIOD 7-1-57 TO 10-31-58 1957 - 1958, TMs (Box-folder 9:033)
  ALSO, JOURNALS AVAILABLE IN OTOLARYNGOLOGY
- UVA HOSPITAL DEPT. OF OTOLARYNGOLOGY: OUTLINE OF TEACHING PLAN 1958, AMs, TMs (Box-folder 9:034)
  FROM AMA FILE
- LIST OF OPERATIONS PERSONALLY PERFORMED BY INDIVIDUAL RESIDENTS October 1958, TMs (Box-folder 9:035)
- ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES, COUNCIL OF TEACHING HOSPITALS 1965 - 1978, TL (2), TLS (2) (Box-folder 9:036)
- INCOME & EXPENSE SURVEY (FISCAL YEAR 1977 DATA) FOR UNIVERSITY OWNED TEACHING HOSPITALS 1978, Questionnaire (Box-folder 9:038)
  FROM ASSOCIATION OF AMERICAN MEDICAL COLLEGES
- NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR INFANTILE PARALYSIS CORRESPONDENCE 1953 - 1955, TMs, TLS (2), TL, Article Offprint (Box-folder 9:039)
- NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR INFANTILE PARALYSIS CORRESPONDENCE 1955 - 1956, TLS (3), TL, TMs (Box-folder 9:040)
- NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR INFANTILE PARALYSIS CORRESPONDENCE 1958 - 1964, TLS (3), TL (2), TMs (Box-folder 9:041)
- POLIOMYELITIS ANNUAL STATISTICAL REVIEWS 1955 - 1957, TLS, Pamphlets (Box-folder 9:042)
  FROM NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR INFANTILE PARALYSIS
- POLIOMYELITIS ANNUAL STATISTICAL REVIEWS 1957 - 1960, TLS, Pamphlets (Box-folder 9:043)
- THE BROADENED CHAPTER PATIENT AID PROGRAM OF THE NATIONAL FOUNDATION May 1, 1959, TMs (Box-folder 9:044)
- NEW INFORMATION FOR PHYSICIANS ON THE SALK POLIOMYELITIS VACCINE June 1956, Pamphlet (Box-folder 9:045)
  FROM THE NATIONAL FOUNDATION FOR INFANTILE PARALYSIS
- DATA PROCESSING FILE CORRESPONDENCE 1965 - 1970, TL, ALS, TLS (Box-folder 9:046)
- A PROPOSAL TO THE STATE COUNCIL ON HIGHER EDUCATION FROM THE UVA MEDICAL CENTER TO ACQUIRE A NEW DATA PROCESSING SYSTEM April 9, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 9:047)
  FROM THE DATA PROCESSING FILE
- SUPPLEMENTAL DATA FOR PROPOSAL OF APRIL 9, 1970 FOR A NEW DATA PROCESSING SYSTEM June 18, 1970, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 9:048)
  FROM DATA PROCESSING FILE
- REQUEST FOR PROPOSALS FOR A DATA PROCESSING SYSTEM September 14, 1970, TMs (Box-folder 9:049)
- DATA PROCESSING SYSTEM BIO EVALUATION 1970?, TMs (Box-folder 9:050)
- LIST OF SOME OPERATIONS PERFORMED BY MEMBERS OF THE OTOLARYNGOLOGY DEPARTMENT 1952, AMs (Box-folder 9:032)
- ELECTROENCEPHALOGRAM CORRESPONDENCE FILE 1953 - 1962, TLS, AL, TL (Box-folder 10:001)
- NEUROLOGY AND PSYCHIATRY CORRESPONDENCE 1958, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:002)
- NEUROLOGY AND PSYCHIATRY CORRESPONDENCE 1959, TL, ALS, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:003)
- NEUROLOGY AND PSYCHIATRY CORRESPONDENCE FILE 1960, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:004)
- NEUROLOGY AND PSYCHIATRY CORRESPONDENCE FILE 1961, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:005)
- NEUROLOGY & PSYCHIATRY CORRESPONDENCE & MEMORANDA 1962, TL, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:006)
- NEUROLOGY & PSYCHIATRY CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1963 - 1964, TL, TMs, ALS, TLS (2) (Box-folder 10:007)
- ANNUAL REPORT OF THE NEUROLOGY & PSYCHIATRY CLINIC 1959, TMs (Box-folder 10:008)
- ANNUAL REPORT: MENTAL HEALTH CLINICS, UVA HOSPITAL 1963-1964 1963 - 1964, TLS, TMs (Box-folder 10:009)
- 5TH REPORT OF THE IN-SERVICE EXCHANGE TRAINING PROGRAM, SOUTHERN REGIONAL EDUCATIONAL BOARD, ATLANTA GEORGIA August 1954, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 10:010)
- PSYCHIATRY RESIDENCY TRAINING PROGRAM, DEPARTMENT OF PSYCHIATRY, SCHOOL OF MEDICINE April 1961, TLS, Pamphlet (Box-folder 10:011)
- SUMMARY OF PSYCHOLOGICAL ACTIVITIES, UVA HOSPITAL NEUROLOGY & PSYCHIATRY CLINIC 1962 - 1963, TMs (Box-folder 10:012)
- MENTAL HEALTH CLINIC CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1964 - 1965, TL, TLS (2), Newsclipping (Box-folder 10:013)
- PROPOSAL FOR A REGIONAL COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH CENTER December 1963, TMs (Box-folder 10:014)
  FROM MENTAL HEALTH CLINIC FILE
- MINUTES OF COMMUNITY HEALTH CENTER PLANNING COMMITTEE February 1964, TMs (Box-folder 10:015)
- REPORT OF THE 8TH CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICT OF VA. REGIONAL STUDY GROUP FOR COMPREHENSIVE MENTAL HEALTH PLANNING November 1964, TMs (Box-folder 10:016)
- COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH CENTER CORRESPONDENCE AND MEMORANDA 1967 - 1970, TL, TLS (2), TMs (Box-folder 10:017)
- COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH CENTER FOR CHARLOTTESVILLE AND ALBEMARLE COUNTY August 1968, Architect's drafts (Box-folder 10:018)
- APPLICATION FOR STAFFING GRANT, COMMUNTIY MENTAL HEALTH CENTER 1970, TMs, TLS (Box-folder 10:019)
- APPLICATION FOR STAFFING GRANT FROM CHARLOTTESVILLE-ALBEMARLE COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH SERVICES BOARD 1970, TMs (Box-folder 10:020)
- AGREEMENTS BETWEEN CHARLOTTESVILLE-ALBEMARLE COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH SERVICES BOARD AND UVA MEDICAL CENTER March 1970, TDoc (Box-folder 10:021)
- AGREEMENT BETWEEN CHARLOTTESVILLE-ALBEMARLE COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH BOARD & DEPARTMENT OF PSYCHIATRY OF UVA HOSPITAL March 1970, TDoc (Box-folder 10:022)
- AGREEMENT BETWEEN CHARLOTTESVILLE-ALBEMARLE COMMUNITY MENTAL HEALTH SERVICES BOARD & UVA MEDICAL CENTER April 1970, TDoc (Box-folder 10:023)